{
    "Harry Potter": [
        {
            "Question": "What Hogwarts house does Harry Potter Belong to?", 
            "Answer": "Gryffindor", 
            "Options":[ 
                "Slytherin", 
                "Hufflepuff", 
                "Ravenclaw"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "How are students sorted into their houses?", 
            "Answer": "Sorting Hat", 
            "Options": [
                "Sorting Test", 
                "Sorting Ceremony", 
                "Sorting Wand"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "What house is Draco Malfoy sorted into?",
            "Answer": "Slytherin", 
            "Options": [
                "RavenClaw", 
                "Hufflepuff",
                "Gryffindor"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "What wandcore does Harry Potters wand have?", 
            "Answer": "Pheonix Feather", 
            "Options": [
                "Unicorn Hair",
                "Dragon Heart String", 
                "Troll Hair"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "In the goblet of fire what did Harry Potter have to rescue from the dragons nest?", 
            "Answer": "A Golden Egg", 
            "Options": [
                "A Broom",
                "A Golden Snitch",
                "A Map"
            ]
        }
    ],

    "One Piece Quiz": [
        {
            "Questions":" What is the name of Monkey D Luffys Devil Fruit ?", 
            "Answer": "Gomu Gomu No Mi", 
            "Options":[
                " Magu Magu No Mi",
                "Goro Goro No Mi",
                "Ope Ope No Mi"
                ]
        },


        {
           " Question": "How many swords does Roronoa Zoro use when fighting ?", 
            "Answer": 3, 
            "Options": [
                1, 
                9,
                2
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "What kind of animal is Tony Chopper ?", 
            "Answer":" Reindeer", 

            "Options": [
                "Otter",
                "Lion",
                "Rabbit"
                ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "What is the name of Monkey D Luffy's first ship?", 
            "Answer": "Going Merry ",
            "Options": [
                "Thousand Sunny", 
                "Red Force",
                "The Flying Dutchman"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "What is painted on Moneky D Luffy's Jolly Roger ?", 
            "Answer": "A Skull and Bones wearing a straw hat", 
            "Options": [
                "A Skull and Bones surronded by sweets", 
                "A Skull and Bones with three scars",
                "A Skull and Bones wearing a top hat"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "PlayStation": [
            {
                "Question": "What is the name of the studio that produced The Last Of Us?", 
                "Answer": "Naughty Dog", 
                "Options": [
                    "343 Studios",
                    "Blizzard",
                    "Sucker Punch"
                ]
            }, 

            {
                "Question": "What Marvel franchise is Insomniac famouse for developing?", 
                "Answer": "Spiderman", 
                "Options":[ 
                    "Wolverine",
                    "The Hulk",
                    "Batman"
                ] 
            },
            
           {
                "Question": "What colour is the PlayStation 5?", 
                "Answer": "White and Black", 
                "Options": [
                    "Black and Blue",
                    "Pink and Red",
                    "Blue and White"
                ]
            },

            {
                "Question": "What is the name of the main character in God of war?", 
                "Answer": "Kratos", 
                "Options": [
                    "Zeus", 
                    "Aries", 
                    "Jeff"
                ] 
            },

            {
                "Question": "How many main line Uncharted games have been released ?", 
                "Answer": "5", 
                "Options":[ 
                    "4",
                    "2",
                    "7"
                ]
            } 
        ],

    "Sports" :[
        {
            "Question": "Which country has won the most soccer World Cups?",         
            "Answer": "Brazil", 
            "Options": [
                "Germany",
                "France",
                "South Africa"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "In which year did China host the Olympics?", 
            "Answer": "2008", 
            "Options": [
                "2004",
                "2012",
                "2000"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "How many rugby World Cups has South Africa won?", 
            "Answer": "3",
            "Options": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "4"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question":"What is the 100m sprint record?", 
            "Answer": "9.58s", 
            "Options": [
                "9.78s",
                "9.85s", 
                "9.52s"
            ]
        },    

        {
            "Question":"Who has the most F1 Driver's Championships?",   
            "Answer": "Lewis Hamilton", 
            "Options": [
                "Fernando Alonso",
                "Sebastian Vettel",
                "NikiLaude"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "Geography" :[
        {
            "Question":"What is the largest continent in size?", 
            "Answer": "Asia", 
            "Options": [
                "Africa",
                "Europe",
                "North America"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question":"Which is the smallest country in size?", 
            "Answer": "Vatican City", 
            "Options": [
                "Naura",
                "Tonga", 
                "Samoa"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question":"In which country is the tallest mountain?", 
            "Answer": "Nepal", 
            "Options": [
                "Switzerland",
                "Greenland",
                "Slovakia"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question":"Which is the largest ocean?", 
            "Answer": "Pacific Ocean",
            "Options": [
                "Atlantic Ocean",
                "Indian Ocean",
                "Arctic Ocean"
            ] 
        },

        {
            "Question":"What is the size of the Sahara desert?", 
            "Answer": "9 200 000 km2", 
            "Options": [
                "10 000 000 km2", 
                "9 500 000 km2 ", 
                "9 000 000 km2"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question":"What is the capital of Italy?", 
            "Answer": "Rome", 
            "Options": [
                "Florence", 
                "Venice", 
                "Naples"
            ]
        } 
    ],

    "Science" : [
        {
            "Question": "What does a 'light year' measure?", 
            "Answer": "Distance", 
            "Options": [
                "Sound", 
                "Time",
                "Speed"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "Photosynthesis is a process created by?",
            "Answer": "Plants", 
            "Options": [
                "Animals", 
                "Food", 
                "Cameras"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "How many bones are in the human body?",
            "Answer": "206", 
            "Options": [
                "106", 
                "156", 
                "256"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "How much of the Earth's surface is covered in water?", 
            "Answer": "70%",
            "Options": [
                "20%",
                "40%",
                "50%"
            ]
        }, 

        {
            "Question": "In which food will you find the most Vitamin C?", 
            "Answer": "Vitamin C", 
            "Options": [
                "Meat",
                "Fish",
                "Cereal"
            ]
        }
    ], 
    "Math":[
        {
            "Question": "121 Divided by 11 is",
            "Answer": "11",
            "Options": [
                "11",
                "10",
                "19",
                "18"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "Solve 3 + 6 ร ( 5 + 4) รท 3 - 7",
            "Answer": "14",
            "Options": [
                "11",
                "16",
                "14",
                "15"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "Solve 23 + 3 รท 3",
            "Answer": "24",
            "Options": [
                "24",
                "25",
                "26",
                "27"
            ]
        },

        {
            "Question": "Add the Decimals 5.23 + 8.79",
            "Answer": "14.02",
            "Options": [
                "14.19",
                "14.11",
                "14.02",
                "14.29"
            ]
        },
        
        {
            "Question": "The Product of 131 x 0 x 300 x 4",
            "Answer": "0",
            "Options": [
                "11",
                "0",
                "46",
                "45"
            ]
        }
    ]

}